Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Clipping file, ca. 1920-1980
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan
  - M
    - Music, School of
      - 1953-1957 (Box 40)
      - 1958-1964 (Box 40)
      - 1964 (Box 40)
    - Music, School of-Extension Program. (Box 40)
      (Includes projects and groups: Intercollegiate Musical Council; Michigan Youth Symphony; Instrumental Music Clinic (Festival); Michigan Music Festival; Michigan State Vocal Association; Michigan Civic Orchestra Association; American Musicological Society; String Teaching Conference; School and Community Orchestra Conferences; Michigan Music Teachers Association; Michigan Schoolmasters Club-Music Conference; High School Music Clinic; Michigan School Band and Orchestra Association; Michigan State Band and Orchestra Festival; High School Music Clinic; School Vocal Music Conference; Michigan State Vocal Association (programs); Conference on Bands, Wind and percussion; Piano Conference; Michigan School Solo and Ensemble Festival; Contemporary Music Festival. see also: Radio ("Festival of Song"); Music, School of-Midwestern Conference; Bands-Extension Program; Bands-High School Band Clinic; Glee Club; Organ (for Conference on Organ Music))
    - Music, School of-Honors Program.
      (see:;Honors Program.)
    - Music, School of-Midwestern Conference on School Vocal and Instrumental Music. 1946- (Box 40)
      (For earlier groups see also: Music, School of-Extension Program; Midwestern Music Conference.)
    - Music, School of-Summer session program
      (For general series see Music, School of. For programs by a special group see that group, e.g.: Stanley Quartet; Chamber Music; Bands-Summer Session Band; Music, School of-Extension)
    - Music Education, Dept. of.
      (see: Music, School of.)
    - Music festivals.
    - Music School Assembly. Student Council group.
    - Music series.
      (Includes: Choral Union Series; Extra Concert Series; May Festival; "Messiah"; Summer Concert Series; Chamber Arts Series; Dance Festival; Dance Series; University Musical Society (and all performances sponsored by University Musical Society except Chamber Music Festival-see below) see also: Music Series-Chamber Music Festival; Hill Auditorium.)
      - 1921-1929 (Box 40)
      - 1930-1933 (Box 40)
      - 1934-1937 (Box 40)
      - 1938-1943 (Box 40)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 40)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 40)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 40)
      - 1949-1950 (Box 40)
      - 1951-June 1952 (Box 40)
      - July 1953-1954 (Box 40)
      - 1954 (Box 41)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 41)
      - 1957 (Box 41)
      - 1958-August 1965 (Box 41)
      - Jan, 1965-August 1969 (Box 41)
      - September 1969-August 1970 (Box 41)
      - September 1970-August 1971 (Box 41)
      - September 1971-August 1972 (Box 41)
      - September 1972-August 1973 (Box 41)
      - September 1973- (Box 41)
    - Music Series-Chamber Music Festival (Box 41)
      (note: only for University Musical Society sponsored Chamber Music Festival. see also: (for other groups): Stanley Quartet; Chamber Music; Music Series (for Chamber Arts Series).)
    - Music teachers.
      (see: Music, School of-Extension Program. Musket. (Men's Union Show) 1956-. see: Union Opera 1956-.)
    - Muslim Students Association
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Africa and Near East.)
  - N
    - NAACP. (Box 41)
      (see card for National Association for the Advancement of Colored People.)
    - N.R.O.T.C.
    - Ralph Naefus Club.
      (see: Philosophy, Dept. of)
    - (John) Nakamura House
      (see: Intercooperative Council, Inc. (card). (folder)-Cooperative rooming and boarding projects.)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP).
      (see: Race Relations; Race Problems (general file); Ann Arbor-Societies-I-N.)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors.
    - National Defense Education Act.
      (see: Loan Funds.)
    - National Intercollegiate Air Meet.
    - National Lawyers Guild.
    - National Moot Court.
      (see: Law School-Case Clubs.)
    - National Music Camp (Interlochen).
      (see: Interlochen Music Camp)
    - National Sanitation Foundation.
      (An independent organization using university facilities. see: Public Health, School of)
    - National Student Association. Started 1946-, 2 folders (Box 41)
      (Includes the International Student Association)
    - National Student Congress, 1950.
    - National Student Cooperative League.
      (see: (card)-Intercoopertive Council, Inc.; (folder)-Cooperative rooming and boarding projects.)
    - National Student League.
      (see: Political Clubs-National Student League.)
    - Natural Resources, School of.
      (Created 1950. Includes Dept. of Conservation, Fisheries; Forestry, Wildlife Management; Wood Technology)
      - 1950-October 1953 (Box 41)
      - November 1953-1962 (Box 41)
      - 1963 (Box 41)
    - Natural Resources in World Affairs. (Box 42)
      (see: Summer Session-Campus Events (1949).)
    - Natural Science Building Exhibits.
      (see: Science. (Except for the gen collection-see Mineralogy, Dept. of))
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Dept. of
      (see: Engineering College-Marine and mechanical.)
    - Naval Reserve Officers Training Corps
      (see: Naval Science, Dept. of.)
    - Naval Science, Dept. of.
      (see also: R.0.T.C. (joint actions); WW2-Army and Navy Education programs; Societies-Military; Ann Arbor-Defense (local non-university reserve units and Armed Forces Day).)
      - NROTC
        - 1923-1954 (Box 42)
        - 1955 (Box 42)
    - Navy Conference Research.
      (Sponsored by the Office of Naval Research and conducted by Dr. Heyns and others in the Psychology Dept. see: Psychology, Dept. of)
    - (Ralph) Neafus Club.
      (see: Political Clubs-Communist; Political Clubs-Progressive Club; Student Workers Federation. Named for a student active in all three groups.)
    - Near East Club.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Africa and the Near East.)
    - Near East Expeditions.
    - Near Eastern Studies, Dept. of. (Box 42)
      (see also: Near Eastern Studies-Expeditions; Fine Arts, Dept. Islamic Art)
    - Near Eastern Studies-Expeditions. (Box 42)
      (Includes: Near East Expeditions: Egypt and Asia Minor (Kelsey and Waterman); Antioch of Psidia, Egypt (Kelsey and others); Fel Umar, Iraq (Waterman); Karamis, Egypt (Starkey, Peterson, Boak, etc.) Near Eastern Studies Expeditions: Syria (Cameron) Persia (Iraq) (Cameron); Mt. Behistun (Cameron). see also: men involved and Kelsey Museum of Archaeology; Near Eastern Studies-Mesopotamia. Expeditions)
    - Near Eastern Studies-Mesopotamia Expedition. At Seleucia to study Parthian history. Led by Waterman. (Box 42)
    - Needs.
      (see: Finances.)
    - Nell Gwyn Company. Amateur groups for the production of Shakespeare's plays.
      (see: Dramatics-Faculty and town groups.)
    - Clifford T. Nelson Award.
    - Nelson International House.
      (see: Cooperative Rooming and Boarding Projects.; Foreign Students-Housing.)
    - Neptune Film Society.
      (see: Moving Pictures.)
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute.
      (see: Psychiatry.)
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute Journal Club.
    - Neurosis Center.
      (see: Veterans Readjustment Center.)
    - New Education Fellowship, 8th International Conference of (Summer, 1941). (Box 42)
    - New Mobilization.
      (see: Activism.)
    - New University Conference (NUC. March 1968-.)
    - Newcomers Guide.
      (see: University Relations Service. Newman Club. see: Religion-Churches-Catholic.)
    - News Dissemination Service.
    - Nichols Arboretum.
    - North Campus. (Box 42)
      (Includes buildings. see also: Phoenix Project; Water Pollution Research; Building Program; Research sponsored by the University see Phoenix Project-Research; Engineering, College of-; North Campus; various departments-; Research sponsored by non-University firms see: North Campus-Research by non-University firms.)
    - North Campus-Research by non-university firms. (Box 42)
      (Includes: Parke, Davis and Co.; Bendix Aviation Corp. (Systems Division).)
    - North Campus 'Fluids Lab. Building
      (see: North Campus. Activities see: Engineering, College of-North Campus and departments doing research or North Campus-Research by non-University firms.)
    - Novelaires. Quartet with the Men's Glee Club.
      (see: Glee Clubs.)
    - Nu Sigma Nu. Medical Fraternity.
    - Nuclear Engineering Congresses.
    - Nuclear Engineering Program.
    - Nurses. (Box 42)
      (see also: Hospitals; Medical School)
  - O
    - Oaths (loyalty).
      (see: Radicals (general) December 1941 Societies-Faculty (for A.A.U.P. attitudes); Employees (for research staff, etc.))
    - Observatory.
      (Includes Observatory Journal Club and open house nights.)
      - 1920-1933 (Box 42)
      - 1934-1944 (Box 42)
      - 1945-1954 (Box 42)
      - 1955-1964 (Box 42)
      - 1965- (Box 42)
    - Occupational Therapy.
      (see: Hospitals.)
    - Oceanography.
      (see: Meteorology and Oceanography.)
    - Odonto Ball.
    - Off Campus Expansion.
      (see: Expansion)
    - Office of Naval Research.
      (see: For IRIA projects see:)
    - Engineering, College of-Engineering Research Institute; For NCA programs
      (see: Psychology, Dept. of.)
    - Office of Research Administration (ORA).
      (Est. January 1961 through reorganization of the Univ. Research Institute (UMRI, now defunct). ORA will be responsible for all categories of Univ. research, but will not itself conduct research. see Institute of Science and Technology; Division of Research Development and Administration)
    - Office of Special Services and Programs (Box 42)
    - Office of Student Affairs.
      (see: Dean-Men; Dean-Women; Student Affairs, Office of (1962-).)
    - Office personnel.
      (see: Employees.)
    - Offices.
      (For location of temporary offices for any department see: Administration)
    - Official Publications.
      (see: Publications.)
    - Officials Club.
      (see: Athletics-Intramural-Women.)
    - Oil Can Award.
      (see: Sigma Delta Chi.)
    - Okayama University, Japan. Social Science Research Center.
      (From 1950-6 a Field Station 1956-created Social Science Research Center. see: Far Eastern Studies.)
    - Old Age.
    - (El) Oliver School.
      (see: Vocational Education and Practical Arts, .,Dept. of)
    - Olympic Ball.
      (Dance sponsored by PE Dept. for men, PE Dept. for women, and M Club. see Physical Education for Men, Dept. of)
    - Omega Phi (Women's literary society).
    - Omicron Kappa Upsilon. Dental Honorary Society.
    - "Once" Festival, Concerts.
      (see: Music; University Activities Center (when part of Creative Arts Festival).)
    - Opera.
      (Joint production of the Schools of Music and Speech. Includes also operas from the Repertory Players (summer session) and early Gilbert and Sullivan operettas. For current operettas see: Dramatics-Repertory Players; Gilbert and Sullivan Society.)
      - 1930-1956 (Box 42)
      - 1957 (Box 42)
    - Operation 4006. (Radio Broadcasting of the Speech Dept.)
    - Operation Tracer.
      (soil study. see: Phoenix Project-Research)
    - Opportunity Awards.
      (see: Scholarships.)
    - Oratorical Association., 1921-1956
      - 1921-1928 (Box 42)
      - 1928/29-1929/30 (Box 42)
      - Box 421930/31/-1932/33 (Box 42)
      - 1933/34-1935/36 (Box 42)
      - 1936/37-1940/41 (Box 42)
      - 1941/42-1945/46 (Box 42)
      - 1946/47/1948/49 (Box 42)
      - 1948/49-1953/54 (Box 42)
      - 1955- (Box 42)
    - Oratorical Series. (1936)
    - Orchestras (Box 43)
      (Includes materials on the Symphony Orchestra, Little Symphony, Summer Session Symphony, University String Orchestra, Repertory Orchestra, Extension Orchestra, University Concert Orchestra (amateurs), Symphonic Swing Orchestra, Michigan Orchestral Festival, Michigan Civic Orchestra Association, University Philharmonia)
      - 1930-1955 (Box 43)
      - 1956- (Box 43)
    - Organ. (Box 43)
      (Includes concerts. Conference on Organ Music.)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies.
      (A cooperative program maintaining Center for Tropical Studies in San Juan, Costa Rica). see: Biological Sciences, Division of)
    - Oriental Language and Literature, Dept. of (1948)
    - Orientation.
      (see: Freshmen)
    - Orthotics Research Project.
      (see: Medical Center.)
    - (Harold) Osterweil House.
      (see: (card)-Inter-cooperative Council, Inc.; (folder Cooperative rooming and boarding projects))
    - Outdoor Education Club.
      (see: Societies-Outing.)
    - Outing.
      (see: Societies-Outing. r)
    - The Overland Stage, see Dramatics-Student group
    - (Robert) Owen House.
      (see: (card)-Inter-cooperative Council, Inc.; (folder)-Cooperative rooming and boarding projects.)
  - P
    - P Bell (Pretzel Bell).
      (see: Traditions)
    - Pacific Expeditions. Led by Prof. Pollock.
      (see: Expeditions-Pacific.)
    - Pakistan Club.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Asia Paleontology. see: Geology, Dept. of)
    - Palladium. Early yearbook of the fraternities.
    - (Alice Freeman) Palmer House.
      (see: (card)-Intercooperative Council, Inc. (folder)-Cooperative rooming and boarding projects.)
    - Palmer (Alice Freeman) Professorship.
      (see: Alumnae Council.)
    - Pan Hellenic.
      (see: Sororities. Pan Hellenic.)
    - Papyri Conservation Task Force.
    - Papyri Collections.
      (see: Classical. Studies, Dept. of; Library-Manuscripts and Papyri Faculty-Kelsey, Francis W.)
    - Parents' Education Institute.
      (see: Extension-Parent-Teacher program.)
    - Parke, Davis, Co.
      (see: North Campus-Research by non-university firms.)
    - Parking System and Regulations. (Box 43)
      (see also: Students'. Autos)
    - Parleys.
      (see: Spring Parley.)
    - Pasteur Institute.
      (see: Medical School; medical School-Research.)
    - Pastors' Conference.
      (see: Extension-Pastors' Conference.)
    - Patterns of American Culture: Contributions of the Negro
    - Peace Corps, 1961 (Box 43)
      (see also: U.S. Peace Corps.)
    - Peace Movements.
      (see also: Peace-War (general file); Peace Corps; Center for Research on Conflict Resolution; Pegasus Club. (see: Riding)
      - 1935-1937 (Box 43)
      - 1937/38-1938/39 (Box 43)
      - 1939/40-1961 (Box 43)
      - 1962- (Box 43)
    - (Edward) Pendleton Fellowships.
    - Pendleton Library.
    - Penny Carnival.
      (see: Women-Penny Carnival.)
    - Pensions.
    - Peoples' Songs, Inc.
      (see: Glee Clubs-Misc.)
    - Pep Band.
      (see: Bands-Wolverine and Varsity)
    - Pep Rallies.
    - Pershing Rifles.
    - Persian Club.
    - Personnel.
    - Perspectives. Literary supplement. to the Daily.
      (see: Student Publications-Literary.)
    - Pharmacology, Dept. of.
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 43)
    - Phi Alpha Delta (Legal fraternity).
      (see: Societies-Law School Phi Alpha Kappa. see: Professional Fraternities)
    - Phi Beta Kappa.
      (see: Societies-Phi Beta Kappa)
    - Phi Chi. Professional Medical Fraternity.
    - Phi Chi Theta. (National Prof. Businesswomen's Frat.)
    - Phi Delta Chi. National Professional Pharmacy Frat.
    - Phi Delta Delta. Women's legal society.
    - Phi Delta Epsilon. Medical Fraternity.
      (see: Societies' Medical School.)
    - Phi Delta Kappa. National Honorary Education Society.
    - Phi Epsilon Kappa. National Honorary Physical Education Fraternity.
      (see: Athletics-Societies.)
    - Phi Eta Sigma.
      (see: Societies-Phi Eta Sigma.)
    - Phi Kappa Phi. see; Societies-Phi Kappa Phi.
    - Phi Lambda Kappa.
      (see: Professional Fraternities.)
    - Phi Lambda Theta.
      (see: societies-Education.)
    - Phi Lambda Upsilon. (National honorary chemical society).
      (see: Societies-Chemistry.)
    - Phi Mu Alpha. Sinfonia. National Music Fraternity.
      (see: Societies-Music.)
    - Phi Sigma 1915-. (Biological Honorary Fret.)
      (see: Zoology Dept.)
    - Phi Rho Sigma. Professional Medical Fraternity.
    - Phi Tau Alpha. Latin and Greek Honorary.
    - Phileutherian Society.
    - Philippine Fund Drive.
      (see: Student Government (1950))
    - PEN.
      (see: Physical Education for Men, Dept. of)
    - Philippine-Michigan Club.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies S.A. and Philippines)
    - Philippines Expedition. Led by Dr. Guthe.
    - Philippines. University. Institute of Public Administration.
      (see: Institute of Public Administration)
    - (Henry) Phillips Scholarships.
    - Philosophical Club.
    - Philosophy, Dept. of (Box 43)
    - Phoenix Project.
      (Includes fund raising. buildings, and general data. see also: Phoenix Project-Research; Phoenix Project-Institutes and Conference Engineering, College of-North Campus; Engineering, College of-ERI; North Campus (buildings).)
      - 1949-1949 (Box 43)
      - 1950 (Box 43)
      - 1951-1954 (Box 43)
      - 1955- (Box 43)
    - Phoenix Project-Institutes and Conferences. (Box 43)
      (Includes also allied agencies and societies.)
    - Phoenix Project-Research.
      (Includes Alice Crocker Lloyd Memorial Isotope Research Lab.; Alice Crocker Lloyd Radiation Therapy Center, Phoenix Radioisotope Lab.; Plant Nutrition Lab., 'Phoenix Radiocarbon Dating Lab.; Fission Products Lab; Institute for Regional Research; see also: Institute of Industrial Health; Institute for Social Research-SRC; Engineering, College of-ERI)
      - 1948-1957 (Box 43)
      - 1958- (Box 43)
    - Phoenix Radioisotope Laboratory.
    - Photography.
      (see: Contests-Club Societies-G-P; Collection-/ Fine Arts, Dept. of; Photographic Services/ Service Enterprises Courses/ Architecture and Design, College of)
    - Photoreproduction Services. (Box 43)
    - Physical Anthropology Laboratory.
    - Physical Education Club. for Men,.
      (for Women. see Athletics-Societies)
    - Physical Education for Men, Dept. of (PEM) 1921-(?)
      (Includes general information, clinics for men and women, Olympic Ball, coaching school, Waterman Gym, WW2; special training programs, etc. For intramural sports see: Athletics-Intramural. For intercollegiate sports see: Athletics, Athletics (list)
      - 1920-1939 (Box 43)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 43)
    - Physical Education for Women, Dept. of 1927-
      (Includes administration of required athletics, building program (Barbour Gym, Women's Athletic Bldg., Palmer Field), staff, etc. see also: Athletics-W.A.A.; Athletics (list of individual sports.)
      - 1920-1934 (Box 43)
      - 1935- (Box 43)
    - Physics, Dept. of.
      (Includes Biophysical Research Center, (before 1960))
      - 1923-1934 (Box 43)
      - 1935-1941 (Box 43)
      - 1932- (Box 43)
    - Physics Club.
    - Pi Kappa Lambda. National Honorary Society.
    - Pi Lambda Theta. National Education Honorary for Women.
    - Pi Sigma Alpha. Political Science Honorary 1920-
      (see: Political Science, Dept. of)
    - Pi Tau PI Sigma. Signal Corps honorary.
    - Pi Tau Sigma (Mechanical Eng. Frat.).
    - Piano Conference 1950-
    - Pictures-Loan.
      (see: Art Print Loan Collection. (For those loaned to schools see Extension Audio-Visual Education Center).)
    - Pilot Project.
      (see: Literary College. (for material on Honors Housing, see: Dormitories (General).)
    - PIRGIM. See Public Interest Research Group
    - Placement Services.
      (see: Bureau of Appointments and Occupational Info. Name of Agency was changed to Placement Services, September 1968.)
    - Planaria Research Group.
      (see: Psychology, Dept. of; Faculty-McConnell, James V.)
    - Plant Department.
      (see: Buildings and Grounds. see also: Employees.)
    - Plant Nutrition Lab.
    - Plasma Engineering Laboratory.
      (see: Engineering, College of-North Campus.)
    - Plates. (Box 43)
    - Play Production (3 Act Plays)
      (see also: English Dept.; Dramatics (1 Act and misc.); Dramatics-Repertory Players (summer session); Dramatics-Dramatic Festival)
      - 1924-1931 (Box 44)
      - 1932-1936 (Box 44)
      - 1937-1944 (Box 44)
      - 1945-1951 (Box 44)
      - 1952-1956 (Box 44)
      - 1957- (Box 44)
    - Play Production (summer session).
      (see: Dramatics-Repertory Players.)
    - Players.
      (see: Dramatics-Student groups (misc.))
    - Plays. see card for Dramatics.
    - Poetry Readings.
      (see: Lecture and Poetry Series. Poetry Society. see Societies-Literary.)
    - Point System. (Box 44)
    - Poison Information and Therapy Control Center.
      (see: Hospitals (1958-).)
    - Polar Research Laboratory (i.e. Glacial Geology and Polar Research. Lab. Estab. 1961).
    - Police.
      (see: Crime; Students' Automobiles; Community Relations; Extension-Law Enforcement;)
    - Poliomyelitis Vaccine Evaluation Center.
      (see: Public health, School of; Faculty-Dr. Francis.)
    - Polish Language.
      (see: Slavic Languages and Literatures, Dept. of.)
    - Political Clubs. (Box 44)
      (Contains general items. Contains misc. groups: University Progressive Council, Liberal Discussion Group, National Student Congress Against War, Michigan League Against War, Committee for the Advance of Capitalistic Enterprise, Michigan Party, Michigan Student Alliance, etc. Independent Socialist Club. For major individual clubs see the cards following: see also: Radicals; Race Problems; Free Speech.)
    - Political Clubs-Americans for Democratic Action (ADA). Political (Box 44)
    - Clubs-Challenge. (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-Civil Liberties Committee. (Box 44)
      (see also: Censorship)
    - Political Clubs-Committee for Liberal Action. (Box 44)
      (Formed as the Pest-war Council, 1942 to study post-war problems. Reorganized in 1945 as the Committee for Liberal Action.)
    - Political Clubs-Communist. (Box 44)
      (see also: Radicals (for investigations by congressional committees); Michigan Forum (debates).)
    - Political Clubs-Democrats.
      (Contains Young Democrats and allied groups.)
      - 1928-1955 (Box 44)
      - 1956- (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-International Relations. (Box 44)
      (see also: Political Clubs (for societies for peace); Political Clubs-United World Federalists; Political Clubs-Committee for Liberal Action.)
    - Political Clubs-Labor Youth League. (Box 44)
      (Succeeded the Michigan YDA). see also: Radicals (for congressional investigation, 1954.))
    - Political Clubs-Michigan Youth for Democratic Action. (MYDA).
      (Affiliated with American Youth for Democracy. Includes the Michigan Committee for Academic Freedom.)
      - 1940-1947 (Box 44)
      - 1947- (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-National Student League. (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-Non-partisan groups. (Box 44)
    - Political Club-Political Issues Club 1956-. (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-Progressive Club
      (Affiliated with American Student Union Published "Student Advocate".)
      - 1935-1939 (Box 44)
      - 1940- (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-Progressives. (Box 44)
      (Includes Young Progressive Citizens of America, Progressive Party, etc.; Students for Effective Action. see also: Political Clubs-Democrats (for Students for Wallace).)
    - Political Clubs-Republicans.
      (Contains Young Republicans and allied groups. see also: Political Clubs-Democrats (for jt. debates).)
      - 1926-1955 (Box 44)
      - 1956- (Box 44)
    - Political Clubs-Round Table Club. (Box 44)
      (Affiliated with League for Industrial Democracy. see also: Political Clubs-Vanguard Club.)
    - Political Clubs-Socialist. (Box 44)
      (Includes Democratic Socialist Club, League for Liberal Action. see also: Coop. Rooming and Boarding Houses-(for "Socialist House").)
    - Political Clubs-Student Defenders of Democracy. (Box 44)
      (Affiliated with Student League of America)